[
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "OCM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "SCENEWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "SCENEWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "Scenewise Aerosol Optical Depth over Land"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "2024-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "Scenewise Aerosol Optical Depth over Land"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06OCM_L2C_AD?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:OCM] [Product:E06OCM_L2C_AD] [Product Description:Scenewise Aerosol Optical Depth over Land] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:SCENEWISE] [Start Date:2024-10-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "OCM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "Daily Aerosol Optical Depth over Land"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "2023-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "Daily Aerosol Optical Depth over Land"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06OCM_L3_AD?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:OCM] [Product:E06OCM_L3_AD] [Product Description:Daily Aerosol Optical Depth over Land] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2023-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "L4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "OCM"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L4] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "2023-07-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06OCM_L4_AC?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:OCM] [Product:E06OCM_L4_AC] [Product Description:The Analyzed Chlorophyll products are generated by combining OCM-3 derived chlorophyll observations with coupled physical-biogeochemical model simulation of chlorophyll using particle filter based assimilation technique. The model utilized is MOM5, coupled with biogeochemical model TOPAZ.] [Processing Level:L4] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2023-07-17] [End Date:2025-03-10] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "time-ordered Earth-located sigma0s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L1B_SIG?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L1B_SIG] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L1B Product contains time-ordered Earth-located sigma0s] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "flagged sigma0s in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L2A_SIG12?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L2A_SIG12] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L2A Product contains flagged sigma0s in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "flagged sigma0s in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L2A_SIG25?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L2A_SIG25] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L2A Product contains flagged sigma0s in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "flagged wind vectors in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L2B_WV12?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L2B_WV12] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L2B Product contains flagged wind vectors in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "flagged wind vectors in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L2B_WV25?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L2B_WV25] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L2B Product contains flagged wind vectors in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L3_SIG12_HH] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L3 Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2024-12-31] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L3_SIG12_VV] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L3 Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2024-12-31] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L3_SIG25_HH] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L3 Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L3_SIG25_VV] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L3 Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "EOS-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "flagged wind vectors in global grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "2024-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "EOS-06 Scatterometer L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E06SCT_L3_WW12?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-06] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:E06SCT_L3_WW12] [Product Description:EOS-06 Scatterometer L3 Product contains flagged wind vectors in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2024-06-01] [End Date:2024-12-31] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L1B_STD] [Product Description:Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "L1C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "2016-10-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER] [Product Description:IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection for Asian Sector] [Processing Level:L1C] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-03] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "L1C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "TIR1, TIR2, WV, VIS, SWIR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "2016-10-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "Level1 IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L1C_SGP] [Product Description:Level1 IMAGER 6 channel data of TIR1, TIR2, WV, VIS, SWIR, MIR Bands in Mercator projection] [Processing Level:L1C] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-03] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "1 km"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "one visible and one SWIR band"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "2025-03-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L2B_CMK] [Product Description:INSAT-3DR VHRR measures radiances in one visible and one SWIR band at 1 km spatial resolution, one MIR and two TIR bands at 4 km resolution, and one WV band at 8 km resolution. Radiances from 3 IR spectral bands TIR ?1 , TIR ?2 and MIR which are of same resolution of 4km are used in the INSAT cloud mask algorithm to estimate whether a given view of the earth surface is unobstructed by clouds] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3R IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "2018-11-30"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3R IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L2B_CTP] [Product Description:Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3R IMAGER] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2018-11-30] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L2B_HEM] [Product Description:This product is derived on the basis of Hydro-Estimator method. It measures precipitation over Indian Region encompassing area between longitudes 30\u00b0E -to130\u00b0E and latitudes 50\u00b0N- 50\u00b0S.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "infrared (IR) brightness temperatures (Tbs, 10.7 \u00b5m observations"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "2025-03-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "INSAT multispectral Rainfall Algorithm Technique"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L2B_IMC] [Product Description:INSAT multispectral Rainfall Algorithm Technique (IMSRA) is one of the main operational rainfall retrieval algorithms for INSAT-3DR. This algorithm estimates precipitation based on non-linear power law relationship established between infrared (IR) brightness temperatures (Tbs, 10.7 \u00b5m observations) and TRMM-PR surface rain rate. Based on a number of case studies and research works carried out, a further refinement of the algorithm was made.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-11-08] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Land surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Land surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L2B_LST] [Product Description:Land surface temperature (LST) is a key parameter in the land surface processes. LST is very useful input to various models related to agrometeorology, ecology, hydrology and climate.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "2025-03-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L2B_OLR] [Product Description:Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux, thermally emitted from earth atmosphere system, is estimated by applying regression equation relating OLR flux with INSAT-3DR Imager observed WV (6.7&#956;m) and thermal infrared (TIR-1 10.5 &#956;m and TIR-2 11.5 &#956;m) radiances. The coefficients of the regression equations are determined from results of the Radiative Transfer Model simulation with various atmospheric conditions] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "Sea surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "Sea surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3RIMG_L2B_SST] [Product Description:Sea surface temperature is derived from split thermal window channels (TIR1, TIR2) during daytime and using additional mid IR window channel (MIR) during night time over cloud free oceanic regions. The most important part of the SST retrieval from IR observations is the atmospheric correction, especially over tropics. This correction is determined through a suitable characterization of tropical atmospheres in radiative transfer model to simulate the brightness temperatures of INSAT-3DR channels a] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3RSND_L1B_SA1] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:7 PER DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "2018-02-14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3RSND_L1B_SA2] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A2 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:5 PER DAY] [Start Date:2018-02-14] [End Date:2023-02-22] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3RSND_L1B_SB1] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:3 PER DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3RSND_L2B_SA1] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:7 PER DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "2018-01-24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3RSND_L2B_SA2] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A2 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:5 PER DAY] [Start Date:2018-01-24] [End Date:2023-02-22] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "2016-10-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3RSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DR] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3RSND_L2B_SB1] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:3 PER DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L1B_STD] [Product Description:Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "L1C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER] [Product Description:IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection for Asian Sector] [Processing Level:L1C] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "L1C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "WV, VIS, SWIR, MIR Bands in Mercator projection"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "Level1 IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L1C_SGP] [Product Description:Level1 IMAGER 6 channel data of TIR1, TIR2, WV, VIS, SWIR, MIR Bands in Mercator projection] [Processing Level:L1C] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "1 km"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "one visible and one SWIR band"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "2025-03-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3S VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L2B_CMK] [Product Description:INSAT-3S VHRR measures radiances in one visible and one SWIR band at 1 km spatial resolution, one MIR and two TIR bands at 4 km resolution, and one WV band at 8 km resolution. Radiances from 3 IR spectral bands TIR-1 , TIR-2 and MIR which are of same resolution of 4km are used in the INSAT cloud mask algorithm to estimate whether a given view of the earth surface is unobstructed by clouds] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-06-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3S IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "2024-07-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3S IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L2B_CTP] [Product Description:Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3S IMAGER] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-07-13] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L2B_HEM] [Product Description:This product is derived on the basis of Hydro-Estimator method. It measures precipitation over Indian Region encompassing area between longitudes 30\u00c3\u0083\u00c2\u0082\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0E -to130\u00c3\u0083\u00c2\u0082\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0E and latitudes 50\u00c3\u0083\u00c2\u0082\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0N- 50\u00c3\u0083\u00c2\u0082\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b0S.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "infrared (IR) brightness temperatures"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "INSAT multispectral Rainfall Algorithm Technique"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L2B_IMC] [Product Description:INSAT multispectral Rainfall Algorithm Technique (IMSRA) is one of the main operational rainfall retrieval algorithms for INSAT-3S. This algorithm estimates precipitation based on non-linear power law relationship established between infrared (IR) brightness temperatures (Tbs, 10.7 \u00c3\u0083\u00c2\u0082\u00c3\u0082\u00c2\u00b5m observations) and TRMM-PR surface rain rate. Based on a number of case studies and research works carried out, a further refinement of the algorithm was made.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Land surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "2024-06-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Land surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L2B_LST] [Product Description:Land surface temperature (LST) is a key parameter in the land surface processes. LST is very useful input to various models related to agrometeorology, ecology, hydrology and climate.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-06-11] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Total outgoing longwave radiation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "2025-03-11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L2B_OLR] [Product Description:Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux, thermally emitted from earth atmosphere system, is estimated by applying regression equation relating OLR flux with INSAT-3S Imager observed WV (6.7&#956;m) and thermal infrared (TIR-1 10.5 &#956;m and TIR-2 11.5 &#956;m) radiances. The coefficients of the regression equations are determined from results of the Radiative Transfer Model simulation with various atmospheric conditions] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "Sea surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "Sea surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SIMG_L2B_SST?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3SIMG_L2B_SST] [Product Description:Sea surface temperature is derived from split thermal window channels (TIR1, TIR2) during daytime and using additional mid IR window channel (MIR) during night time over cloud free oceanic regions. The most important part of the SST retrieval from IR observations is the atmospheric correction, especially over tropics. This correction is determined through a suitable characterization of tropical atmospheres in radiative transfer model to simulate the brightness temperatures of INSAT-3S channels a] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3SSND_L1B_SA1] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:7 PER DAY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3SSND_L1B_SB1] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:3 PER DAY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3SSND_L2B_SA1] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:7 PER DAY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "2024-05-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3SSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3DS] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3SSND_L2B_SB1] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:3 PER DAY] [Start Date:2024-05-17] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Fully validated offline Native product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "2013-05-23] [End Date:2019-10-07"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "Fully validated offline Native product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLGPN?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLGPN] [Product Description:Fully validated offline Native product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE] [Start Date:2013-05-23] [End Date:2019-10-07] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:Fully validated offline Native product]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "2019-06-24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "Fully validated offline Native product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLGPN_F?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLGPN_F] [Product Description:Fully validated offline Native product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE] [Start Date:2019-06-24] [End Date:2024-03-04] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Fully validated offline Reduced product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "2013-05-23] [End Date:2018-10-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "Fully validated offline Reduced product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLGPR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLGPR] [Product Description:Fully validated offline Reduced product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE] [Start Date:2013-05-23] [End Date:2018-10-22] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:Fully validated offline Reduced product]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "2018-08-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "Fully validated offline Reduced product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLGPR_F?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLGPR_F] [Product Description:Fully validated offline Reduced product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE] [Start Date:2018-08-13] [End Date:2024-04-08] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "2013-05-23] [End Date:2019-06-24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "Fully validated offline Sensor product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLGPS?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLGPS] [Product Description:Fully validated offline Sensor product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE] [Start Date:2013-05-23] [End Date:2019-06-24] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "35 DAYS-CYCLE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "2013-03-14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "Fully validated offline Sensor product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLGPS_F?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLGPS_F] [Product Description:Fully validated offline Sensor product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:35 DAYS-CYCLE] [Start Date:2013-03-14] [End Date:2024-03-04] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Native product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "2013-03-12] [End Date:2020-03-07"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "Interim Geo physical data record, Native product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLIPN?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLIPN] [Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Native product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:3 DAYS] [Start Date:2013-03-12] [End Date:2020-03-07] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Native product]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "2020-02-08"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "Interim Geo physical data record, Native product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLIPN_F?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLIPN_F] [Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Native product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:3 DAYS] [Start Date:2020-02-08] [End Date:2025-03-09] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Reduced product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "2013-03-12] [End Date:2020-03-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "Interim Geo physical data record, Reduced product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLIPR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLIPR] [Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Reduced product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:3 DAYS] [Start Date:2013-03-12] [End Date:2020-03-06] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "SARAL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "ALTIMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "3 DAYS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Reduced product]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "2020-02-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "Interim Geo physical data record, Reduced product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SRLIPR_F?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SARAL] [Sensor:ALTIMETER] [Product:SRLIPR_F] [Product Description:Interim Geo physical data record, Reduced product] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:3 DAYS] [Start Date:2020-02-06] [End Date:2025-03-09] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "EOS-07"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "L1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "MHS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "Geotagged level-1 Brightness temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "2023-03-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "Geotagged level-1 Brightness temperature product derived using Microwave Humidity Sounder"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E07MHSL1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-07] [Sensor:MHS] [Product:E07MHSL1] [Product Description:Geotagged level-1 Brightness temperature product derived using Microwave Humidity Sounder on board Microsat-2B] [Processing Level:L1] [Temporal Resolution:ORBITWISE] [Start Date:2023-03-22] [End Date:2024-12-06] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "EOS-07"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "MHS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "Geotagged level-2 specific humidity profile"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "2023-03-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "Geotagged level-2 specific humidity profile"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E07MHSL2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-07] [Sensor:MHS] [Product:E07MHSL2] [Product Description:Geotagged level-2 specific humidity profile(20 layers),Average column integrated Water vapour(3 layers) derived using Microwave Humidity Sounder on board Microsat-2B] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:ORBITWISE] [Start Date:2023-03-22] [End Date:2024-12-05] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "EOS-07"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "MHS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "Gridded level3 Brightness temperature,specific humidity and integrated water vapoure"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "2023-03-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "Gridded level3 Brightness temperature,specific humidity and integrated water vapoure"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is E07MHSL3?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:EOS-07] [Sensor:MHS] [Product:E07MHSL3] [Product Description:Gridded level3 Brightness temperature,specific humidity and integrated water vapoure derived using Microwave Humidity Sounder on board Microsat-2B] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:ORBITWISE] [Start Date:2023-03-22] [End Date:2024-12-05] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "CCD"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Aerosol optical Depth over Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "2009-04-29"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "Aerosol optical Depth over Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-CCD-AOD?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:CCD] [Product:3A-CCD-AOD] [Product Description:Aerosol optical Depth over Ocean] [Processing Level:0] [Temporal Resolution:3,5,7] [Start Date:2009-04-29] [End Date:2016-08-12] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "CCD"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "3,5,6,7,9,11 GMT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "3,5,6,7,9,11 GMT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "Product Description:10 Day composite-normalised Difference Vegetation Index"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "2008-08-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "10 Day composite-normalised Difference Vegetation Index"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:CCD] [Product:3A-CCD-COMPOSITE-NDV] [Product Description:10 Day composite-normalised Difference Vegetation Index] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:3,5,6,7,9,11 GMT] [Start Date:2008-08-22] [End Date:2016-08-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "L1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "CCD"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "3,5,6,7,9,11 GMT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "3,5,6,7,9,11 GMT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "Co-registered Level-1B data for all 3 bands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "2009-04-29] [End Date:2016-08-12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-CCD-GPS?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:CCD] [Product:3A-CCD-GPS] [Product Description:Co-registered Level-1B data for all 3 bands of INSAT-3A/CCD sensor] [Processing Level:L1] [Temporal Resolution:3,5,6,7,9,11 GMT] [Start Date:2009-04-29] [End Date:2016-08-12] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "CCD"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "data for all 3 Channels- VIS, NIR, SWIR Band"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "2008-08-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "Level 1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-CCD-L1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:CCD] [Product:3A-CCD-L1] [Product Description:Level 1B data for all 3 Channels- VIS, NIR, SWIR Band] [Processing Level:1] [Temporal Resolution:3,5,7] [Start Date:2008-08-22] [End Date:2016-08-12] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "CCD"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "Level 1B Data Over Indian Sector for all 3 channels"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "2008-08-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "Level 1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:CCD] [Product:3A-CCD-L1-INDIAN SECTOR] [Product Description:Level 1B Data Over Indian Sector for all 3 channels - VIS, NIR, SWIR] [Processing Level:1] [Temporal Resolution:3,5,7] [Start Date:2008-08-22] [End Date:2009-07-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "CCD"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "3,5,7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Normalised Difference Vegetation Index"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "2008-08-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "Normalised Difference Vegetation Index"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-CCD-NDV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:CCD] [Product:3A-CCD-NDV] [Product Description:Normalised Difference Vegetation Index] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:3,5,7] [Start Date:2008-08-22] [End Date:2016-08-12] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "both IR and WV channel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "Daily"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-DAILYOLR] [Product Description:Daily (averaged over previous 24 hour) Outgoing Longwave Radiation Derived from INSAT-3A- both IR and WV channel] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2011-03-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "Quantitative Precipitation Estimates"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "Quantitative Precipitation Estimates"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-DAILYQPE] [Product Description:Quantitative Precipitation Estimates based on GPI Algorithm derived using INSAT-3A IR Channel data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2011-03-09] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sea Surface Temperature derived from INSAT-3A IR channel data"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "2009-11-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "Sea Surface Temperature derived from INSAT-3A IR channel data"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-DAILYSST?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-DAILYSST] [Product Description:Sea Surface Temperature derived from INSAT-3A IR channel data] [Processing Level:3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2009-11-17] [End Date:2011-03-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "Upper Tropospheric Humidity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "2009-11-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "Upper Tropospheric Humidity"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-DAILYUTH?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-DAILYUTH] [Product Description:Upper Tropospheric Humidity derived from INSAT-3A IR Channel data] [Processing Level:3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2009-11-09] [End Date:2011-03-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "L1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "BETWEEN 1HR-3HR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "BETWEEN 1HR-3HR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:For every acquisition of INSAT-3A VHRR data"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-L1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-L1] [Product Description:For every acquisition of INSAT-3A VHRR data, currently every 3-hourly] [Processing Level:L1] [Temporal Resolution:BETWEEN 1HR-3HR] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2016-06-21] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "L1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "1HR-3HR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "1HR-3HR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "VIS, IR and WV"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "Level-1B data"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-L1-INDIAN SECTOR] [Product Description:Level-1B data(Indian Sector) for all 3 Channels- VIS, IR and WV for INSAT-3A satellite] [Processing Level:L1] [Temporal Resolution:1HR-3HR] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2016-06-21] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "Outgoing Longwave Radiation derived from INSAT-3A IR Channel Data"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "Outgoing Longwave Radiation derived from INSAT-3A IR Channel Data"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-OLR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-OLR] [Product Description:Outgoing Longwave Radiation derived from INSAT-3A IR Channel Data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:3 HOURLY] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2011-03-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "Quantitative Precipitative Estimates"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "Quantitative Precipitative Estimates"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-QPE?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-QPE] [Product Description:Quantitative Precipitative Estimates based on GPI Alogorithm derived using INSAT-3A IR Channel Data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:3 HOURLY] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2011-03-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sea Surface Temperature derived from INSAT-3A IR channel data"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "Sea Surface Temperature derived from INSAT-3A IR channel data"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-SST?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-SST] [Product Description:Sea Surface Temperature derived from INSAT-3A IR channel data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:3 HOURLY] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2011-03-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "3 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "Upper Tropospheric Humidity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "2009-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "Upper Tropospheric Humidity"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3A-VHR-UTH?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3A] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:3A-VHR-UTH] [Product Description:Upper Tropospheric Humidity derived from INSAT-3A IR Channel data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:3 HOURLY] [Start Date:2009-05-27] [End Date:2011-03-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L1B_STD] [Product Description:Level1 data for Imager 6 channels at half hour interval] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "L1C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L1C_ASIA_MER] [Product Description:IMAGER- 6 channel Level1 data in Mercator projection for Asian Sector] [Processing Level:L1C] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "L1C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "TIR1, TIR2, WV, VIS, SWIR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "Level1 IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L1C_SGP?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L1C_SGP] [Product Description:Level1 IMAGER 6 channel data of TIR1, TIR2, WV, VIS, SWIR, MIR Bands in Mercator projection] [Processing Level:L1C] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "1 km"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "one visible and one SWIR band at 1 km spatial resolution"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "2024-06-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L2B_CMK?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L2B_CMK] [Product Description:INSAT-3D VHRR measures radiances in one visible and one SWIR band at 1 km spatial resolution, one MIR and two TIR bands at 4 km resolution, and one WV band at 8 km resolution. Radiances from 3 IR spectral bands TIR-1 , TIR-2 and MIR which are of same resolution of 4km are used in the INSAT cloud mask algorithm to estimate whether a given view of the earth surface is unobstructed by clouds] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-10-08] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3D IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "2018-11-30"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3D IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L2B_CTP?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L2B_CTP] [Product Description:Cloud top properties derived using INSAT3D IMAGER] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2018-11-30] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "2013-09-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "Product Description:FOG"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L2B_FOG?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L2B_FOG] [Product Description:FOG] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-09-22] [End Date:2013-11-15] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "2013-10-08"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L2B_HEM?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L2B_HEM] [Product Description:This product is derived on the basis of Hydro-Estimator method. It measures precipitation over Indian Region encompassing area between longitudes 30\u00b0E -to130\u00b0E and latitudes 50\u00b0N- 50\u00b0S.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-10-08] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "infrared (IR) brightness temperatures (Tbs, 10.7 \u00b5m observations"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "2024-06-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "INSAT multispectral Rainfall Algorithm Technique"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L2B_IMC?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L2B_IMC] [Product Description:INSAT multispectral Rainfall Algorithm Technique (IMSRA) is one of the main operational rainfall retrieval algorithms for INSAT-3D. This algorithm estimates precipitation based on non-linear power law relationship established between infrared (IR) brightness temperatures (Tbs, 10.7 \u00b5m observations) and TRMM-PR surface rain rate. Based on a number of case studies and research works carried out, a further refinement of the algorithm was made.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2016-01-01] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Land surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "2015-03-04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "Land surface temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L2B_LST?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L2B_LST] [Product Description:Land surface temperature (LST) is a key parameter in the land surface processes. LST is very useful input to various models related to agrometeorology, ecology, hydrology and climate.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2015-03-04] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "IMAGER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "2024-06-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DIMG_L2B_OLR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:IMAGER] [Product:3DIMG_L2B_OLR] [Product Description:Total outgoing longwave radiation (OLR) flux, thermally emitted from earth atmosphere system, is estimated by applying regression equation relating OLR flux with INSAT-3D Imager observed WV (6.7&#956;m) and thermal infrared (TIR-1 10.5 &#956;m and TIR-2 11.5 &#956;m) radiances. The coefficients of the regression equations are determined from results of the Radiative Transfer Model simulation with various atmospheric conditions] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2024-06-18] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L1B_SA1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L1B_SA1] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A1 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:7 PER DAY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2020-05-09] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L1B_SA2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L1B_SA2] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for A2 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:5 PER DAY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2020-05-08] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L1B_SB1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L1B_SB1] [Product Description:Sounder Level1 data for B1 sector] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:3 PER DAY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2018-12-06] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "1 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "1 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Level1 data for SOUNDER 19 Channels"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "2014-04-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "Level1 data for SOUNDER 19 Channels"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L1B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L1B_STD] [Product Description:Level1 data for SOUNDER 19 Channels] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:1 HOURLY] [Start Date:2014-04-18] [End Date:2018-12-05] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "1 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "1 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "18-channel infrared Sounder (plus a visible channel)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "2013-09-24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D carries an 18-channel infrared Sounder"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L2B_PFL?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L2B_PFL] [Product Description:INSAT-3D carries an 18-channel infrared Sounder (plus a visible channel). The algorithm is designed for retrieving vertical profiles of atmospheric temperature and moisture along with total column ozone content in the atmosphere from clear sky infrared radiances in different absorption bands observed through INSAT-3D. Sounder derived profiles include temperature at 40 vertical pressure levels from surface to about 70 km and water vapor in 21 levels from surface to around 15 km.] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:1 HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-09-24] [End Date:2013-10-24] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "7 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L2B_SA1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L2B_SA1] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A1 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:7 PER DAY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2020-05-09] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "5 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for A2 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L2B_SA2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L2B_SA2] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for A2 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:5 PER DAY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2020-05-08] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "INSAT-3D"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "SOUNDER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "3 PER DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "2013-10-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3DSND_L2B_SB1?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:INSAT-3D] [Sensor:SOUNDER] [Product:3DSND_L2B_SB1] [Product Description:Sounder Level2 data for B1 sector] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:3 PER DAY] [Start Date:2013-10-01] [End Date:2018-12-06] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "Cloud Motion Vector and Water Vapour Winds"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "2009-11-03] [End Date:2012-08-06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "Cloud Motion Vector and Water Vapour Winds"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-AMV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-AMV] [Product Description:Cloud Motion Vector and Water Vapour Winds derived from Kalpana IR and WV channel data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2009-11-03] [End Date:2012-08-06] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "Atmospheric Motion Vectors derived using Visible Water vapour and IR bands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "2013-02-21] [End Date:2017-09-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "Atmospheric Motion Vectors"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-AMV-VIS?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-AMV-VIS] [Product Description:Atmospheric Motion Vectors derived using Visible Water vapour and IR bands of Kalpana 1 VHRR data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2013-02-21] [End Date:2017-09-16] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "Kalpana IR Brightness Temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "2009-11-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "Kalpana IR Brightness Temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-BRT?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-BRT] [Product Description:Kalpana IR Brightness Temperature] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2009-11-03] [End Date:2017-09-19] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "Kalpana WV Brightness Temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "2009-11-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "Kalpana WV Brightness Temperature"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-BTW?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-BTW] [Product Description:Kalpana WV Brightness Temperature] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2009-11-03] [End Date:2017-09-19] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "2010-05-04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "Cloud mask"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-CMK?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-CMK] [Product Description:Cloud mask derived using Kalpana-1 IR channel data at every Pixel resolution] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2010-05-04] [End Date:2011-01-04] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "HALF HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "Product Description:Cloud Motion Vector derived from Kalpana IR channel data"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "2008-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "Cloud Motion Vector derived from Kalpana IR channel data"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-CMV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-CMV] [Product Description:Cloud Motion Vector derived from Kalpana IR channel data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:HALF HOURLY] [Start Date:2008-06-01] [End Date:2010-09-08] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "INSAT Multi Chanel Rain; Rainfall estimate"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "2010-06-15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "INSAT Multi Chanel Rain"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-DAILYIMR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-DAILYIMR] [Product Description:INSAT Multi Chanel Rain; Rainfall estimate derived using Indian Multi-Spectral Rainfall algorithm (IMSRA)] [Processing Level:3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2010-06-15] [End Date:2014-04-15] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:0] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "2011-07-17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "Kalpana derived daily insulation product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-DAILYINS?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-DAILYINS] [Product Description:Kalpana derived daily insulation product] [Processing Level:0] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2011-07-17] [End Date:2017-09-10] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "both IR and WV Channel data"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "2008-06-01] [End Date:2017-09-19"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "Daily"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-DAILYOLR?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-DAILYOLR] [Product Description:Daily (averaged over previous 24 hr) Outgoing Longwave Radiation derieved from Kalpana - both IR and WV Channel data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2008-06-01] [End Date:2017-09-19] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "KALPANA-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "VHRR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "Daily Accumulated Quantitative Precipitation Estimates"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "2008-06-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "Daily Accumulated Quantitative Precipitation Estimates"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is K1-VHR-DAILYQPE?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:KALPANA-1] [Sensor:VHRR] [Product:K1-VHR-DAILYQPE] [Product Description:Daily Accumulated Quantitative Precipitation Estimates based on GPI Algoritham derived using Kalpana IR channel data] [Processing Level:2] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2008-06-01] [End Date:2014-04-15] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "MADRAS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "Surface wind speed (m/s), total precipitable water"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13] [End Date:2013-12-21"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "Surface wind speed"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1MADSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:MADRAS] [Product:MT1MADSGPL2A] [Product Description:Surface wind speed (m/s), total precipitable water (g/cm sq.) and cloud liquid water (mg/cm sq.) content over oceans are derived using 18.7, 23.8 and 36.5 GHz channels.Rain flags are generated using 89 GHz.] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2013-12-21] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "L1A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "MADRAS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "Brightness Temperature Product at 18/23/36 , 89 AND 157 GHz"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "Brightness Temperature Product at 18/23/36 , 89 AND 157 GHz"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1MADSL1A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:MADRAS] [Product:MT1MADSL1A] [Product Description:Brightness Temperature Product at 18/23/36 , 89 AND 157 GHz] [Processing Level:L1A] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2013-12-21] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "L1A2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "MADRAS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "Radiance Values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1MADSL1A2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:MADRAS] [Product:MT1MADSL1A2] [Product Description:Radiance Values for infrared, solar, synthetic_LW, total and Visible channels] [Processing Level:L1A2] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2013-12-21] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "MADRAS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "Radiance Values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1MADSL1B?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:MADRAS] [Product:MT1MADSL1B] [Product Description:Radiance Values for infrared, solar, synthetic_LW, total and Visible channels] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2013-12-21] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "MADRAS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "Rain Rate (mm/hr)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "Rain Rate"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1MADSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:MADRAS] [Product:MT1MADSRRL2A] [Product Description:Rain Rate (mm/hr) retrieved from MADRAS, high and low frequency (89, 23.5 , 19 GHz) channels using emission and scattering charateristics of atmospheric and oceanic variables.] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2013-12-21] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "1D"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "ROSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "the behaviour of the excess phase with respect to time of an occulting event"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "2018-12-15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "ROSA Level-1 igr"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is atm_prf_igr_1d?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:ROSA] [Product:atm_prf_igr_1d] [Product Description:ROSA Level-1 igr products which are processed with a latency of 2 days and it provide the profiles of (i) the behaviour of the excess phase with respect to time of an occulting event; (ii) the behaviour of the bending angle with respect to impact parameter of all occulting events; (iii) the behaviour of the refractivity with respect to the height] [Processing Level:1D] [Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION] [Start Date:2016-05-21] [End Date:2018-12-15] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "ROSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "Refractivity, Dry temperature, Temperature, Pressure and Water vapour"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "2016-05-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is atm_prf_igr_l2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:ROSA] [Product:atm_prf_igr_l2] [Product Description:This igr file is in NetCDF format and contains neutral atmospheric profiles of geo physical parameters such as Refractivity, Dry temperature, Temperature, Pressure and Water vapour pressure as well as latitude and longitude profiles at observed geometric heights of ray perigee point.It is processed with a latency of 2-3 days.] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION] [Start Date:2016-05-09] [End Date:2018-12-15] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "1D"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "ROSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "behaviour of the bending angle with respect to impact parameter of all occulting events"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "2011-11-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "ROSA Level-1 igs"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is atm_prf_igs_1d?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:ROSA] [Product:atm_prf_igs_1d] [Product Description:ROSA Level-1 igs products which provide the profiles of (i) the behaviour of the excess phase with respect to time of an occulting event; (ii) the behaviour of the bending angle with respect to impact parameter of all occulting events; (iii) the behaviour of the refractivity with respect to the height] [Processing Level:1D] [Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION] [Start Date:2011-11-22] [End Date:2016-05-27] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "ROSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "Refractivity, Dry temperature, Temperature, Pressure and Water vapour"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "2011-11-22] [End Date:2016-05-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is atm_prf_igs_l2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:ROSA] [Product:atm_prf_igs_l2] [Product Description:This igu file is in NetCDF format and contains neutral atmospheric profiles of geo physical parameters such as Refractivity, Dry temperature, Temperature, Pressure and Water vapour pressure as well as latitude and longitude profiles at observed geometric heights of ray perigee point.It is processed with a latency of around 2 weeks.] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION] [Start Date:2011-11-22] [End Date:2016-05-27] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "1D"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "ROSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "the behaviour of the excess phase with respect to time of an occulting event"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "2016-05-23] [End Date:2018-12-15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "ROSA Level-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is atm_prf_igu_1d?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:ROSA] [Product:atm_prf_igu_1d] [Product Description:ROSA Level-1 igu products which are processed in real time and it provide the profiles of (i) the behaviour of the excess phase with respect to time of an occulting event; (ii) the behaviour of the bending angle with respect to impact parameter of all occulting events; (iii) the behaviour of the refractivity with respect to the height] [Processing Level:1D] [Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION] [Start Date:2016-05-23] [End Date:2018-12-15] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "L2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "ROSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "Refractivity, Dry temperature, Temperature, Pressure and Water vapour"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "2016-05-12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is atm_prf_igu_l2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:ROSA] [Product:atm_prf_igu_l2] [Product Description:This igu file is in NetCDF format and contains neutral atmospheric profiles of geo physical parameters such as Refractivity, Dry temperature, Temperature, Pressure and Water vapour pressure as well as latitude and longitude profiles at observed geometric heights of ray perigee point.It is processed in real time.] [Processing Level:L2] [Temporal Resolution:AS PER DAILY ACQUISITION] [Start Date:2016-05-12] [End Date:2018-12-15] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "SAPHIR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "Layer average relative humidity (%)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "Layer average relative humidity"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SAPSGPL2A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SAPHIR] [Product:MT1SAPSGPL2A] [Product Description:Layer average relative humidity (%) for 6 layers are derived using 6 channels of SAPHIR.] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "L1A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "SAPHIR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "Brightness temperature Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "Brightness temperature Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SAPSL1A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SAPHIR] [Product:MT1SAPSL1A] [Product Description:Brightness temperature Product at S1, S2, S3, S4, S5 and S6 Channel.] [Processing Level:L1A] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "L1A2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "SAPHIR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "Brightness temperature Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "Brightness temperature Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SAPSL1A2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SAPHIR] [Product:MT1SAPSL1A2] [Product Description:Brightness temperature Product at S1, S2, S3, S4, S5 and S6 Channel.] [Processing Level:L1A2] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "SAPHIR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "Brightness temperature Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "2011-10-13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "Brightness temperature Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SAPSL1B?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SAPHIR] [Product:MT1SAPSL1B] [Product Description:Brightness temperature Product at S1, S2, S3, S4, S5 and S6 Channel.] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-10-13] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "SAPHIR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "Rain Rate has been retrieved from SAPHIR channels"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "2015-07-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "Rain Rate has been retrieved from SAPHIR channels"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SAPSRRL2A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SAPHIR] [Product:MT1SAPSRRL2A] [Product Description:Rain Rate has been retrieved from SAPHIR channels using a probabilistic rain identification algorithm and RT simulations supported retrieval algorithm] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2015-07-22] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "SCARAB"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "2011-11-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SCASGPL2A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SCARAB] [Product:MT1SCASGPL2A] [Product Description:This product gives reflected flux at top of atmosphere in Watts/mt.sq and earth emitted long wave flux at TOA in Watts/mt.sq] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-11-03] [End Date:2022-03-13] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "SCARAB"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "Radiance Values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "2011-11-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SCASL1A?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SCARAB] [Product:MT1SCASL1A] [Product Description:Radiance Values for infrared, solar, synthetic_LW, total and Visible channels] [Processing Level:1] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-11-03] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "L1A2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "SCARAB"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "Radiance Values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "2011-11-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SCASL1A2?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SCARAB] [Product:MT1SCASL1A2] [Product Description:Radiance Values for infrared, solar, synthetic_LW, total and Visible channels] [Processing Level:L1A2] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-11-03] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "MEGHATROPIQUES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "SCARAB"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "14 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "Radiance Values"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "2011-11-03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MT1SCASL1B?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:MEGHATROPIQUES] [Sensor:SCARAB] [Product:MT1SCASL1B] [Product Description:Radiance Values for infrared, solar, synthetic_LW, total and Visible channels] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:14 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2011-11-03] [End Date:2022-03-14] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "OCEANSAT-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "12 HOURLY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "12 Hourly"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "12 Hourly Analyzed Wind Vectors"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "2012-01-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "12 Hourly"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is O2-SCT-AWV50?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:OCEANSAT-2] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:O2-SCT-AWV50] [Product Description:12 Hourly Analyzed Wind Vectors are generated by combining Level2B(swath) data from both OSCAT and ASCAT] [Processing Level:4] [Temporal Resolution:12 HOURLY] [Start Date:2012-01-01] [End Date:2014-01-05] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "OCEANSAT-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "Daily Analyzed Wind Vectors"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "2012-01-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "Daily"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:OCEANSAT-2] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:O2-SCT-DAILYAWV50] [Product Description:Daily Analyzed Wind Vectors are generated from Level2B data of OSCAT and ASCAT] [Processing Level:4] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2012-01-01] [End Date:2014-01-06] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "OCEANSAT-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "ORBITWISE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "Backscatter data"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "2011-12-23] [End Date:2014-01-05"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is O2-SCT-HWV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:OCEANSAT-2] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:O2-SCT-HWV] [Product Description:This product is generated making use of Backscatter data at composite slice level as available in L2A product of OSCAT and L2B wind vector product from OSCAT presently at 50km wind vector cells. Wind directions at composite slice location are interpolated utilizing neighbouring cells while wind speed is recalculated using backscattering coefficient and the OSCAT specific GMF. The quality flag of L2B product is reproduced.] [Processing Level:4] [Temporal Resolution:ORBITWISE] [Start Date:2011-12-23] [End Date:2014-01-05] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "time-ordered Earth-located sigma0s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L1B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL1B?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL1B] [Product Description:Scatterometer L1B Product contains time-ordered Earth-located sigma0s] [Processing Level:L1B] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "flagged sigma0s in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL2A25?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL2A25] [Product Description:Scatterometer L2A Product contains flagged sigma0s in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "flagged sigma0s in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L2A"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL2A50?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL2A50] [Product Description:Scatterometer L2A Product contains flagged sigma0s in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2A] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "flagged wind vectors in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL2B25?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL2B25] [Product Description:Scatterometer L2B Product contains flagged wind vectors in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "29-30 ORBIT/DAY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "flagged wind vectors in swath grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL2B50?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL2B50] [Product Description:Scatterometer L2B Product contains flagged wind vectors in swath grid] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:29-30 ORBIT/DAY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "flagged sigma0s in global grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L3s"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL325-HH?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL325-HH] [Product Description:Scatterometer L3s Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "flagged sigma0s in global grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L3s"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL325-VV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL325-VV] [Product Description:Scatterometer L3s Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "flagged sigma0s in global grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L3s"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL350-HH?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL350-HH] [Product Description:Scatterometer L3s Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L3s"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-SIGL350-VV?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-SIGL350-VV] [Product Description:Scatterometer L3s Product contains flagged sigma0s in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "SCATSAT-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "L3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "SCATTEROMETER"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "DAILY"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "flagged wind vectors in global grid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "In-Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "2016-10-18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "Scatterometer L3w"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is S1SCT-WWL325?",
        "answer": "[Category:satellite] [Satellite:SCATSAT-1] [Sensor:SCATTEROMETER] [Product:S1SCT-WWL325] [Product Description:Scatterometer L3w Product contains flagged wind vectors in global grid] [Processing Level:L3] [Temporal Resolution:DAILY] [Start Date:2016-10-18] [End Date:2021-03-01] [Processing Status:In-Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "15F488"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "AGROMET18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "AGROMET18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "2011-02-15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "13.26] [End Date:93.01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Diglipur,Portblair?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:Diglipur,Portblair] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F488] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET18] [Start Date:13.26] [End Date:93.01] [Processing Status:2011-02-15] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "15F0FF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "AGROMET02"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "AGROMET02"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "2010-12-31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "17.34"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:CRIDA Farm,Hayathnagar, Hyderabad] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F0FF] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET02] [Start Date:17.34] [End Date:78.59] [Processing Status:2010-12-31] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "15F464"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "AGROMET06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "AGROMET06"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "2010-12-31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "13.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:SDSC, SHAR, Sriharikota] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F464] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET06] [Start Date:13.62] [End Date:80.23] [Processing Status:2010-12-31] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "15F47F"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "AGROMET15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "AGROMET15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:BIHAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "2010-12-31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "25.98"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "BIHAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:Rajendra Agricultural University, PUSA, Samastipur] [Product Description:BIHAR] [Processing Level:15F47F] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET15] [Start Date:25.98] [End Date:85.67] [Processing Status:2010-12-31] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "15F102"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "AGROMET03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "AGROMET03"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "2010-12-31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "22.80"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:Rice Research Station, Anand Agricultural University, Nawagam.] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:15F102] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET03] [Start Date:22.80] [End Date:72.57] [Processing Status:2010-12-31] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "15F105"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "AGROMET04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "AGROMET04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "2011-04-05"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "21.50"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:Junagadh Agricultural University, Junagadh] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:15F105] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET04] [Start Date:21.50] [End Date:70.44] [Processing Status:2011-04-05] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "15F485"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "AGROMET17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "AGROMET17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "2010-12-31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "23.80"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:Range Office Research Centre, Dhorado, Kutch] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:15F485] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET17] [Start Date:23.80] [End Date:69.50] [Processing Status:2010-12-31] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "15F0FC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "AGROMET01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "AGROMET01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:KARNATAKA]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "2011-07-30"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "16.78] [End Date:75.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "KARNATAKA"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:Regional Agricultural Research Station, Bijapur.] [Product Description:KARNATAKA] [Processing Level:15F0FC] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET01] [Start Date:16.78] [End Date:75.75] [Processing Status:2011-07-30] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "Gopal Pura"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "15F518"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "AGROMET24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "AGROMET24"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:KARNATAKA]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "2012-01-31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "11.76"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "KARNATAKA"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:IISC Bengaluru. (Gopal Pura)] [Product Description:KARNATAKA] [Processing Level:15F518] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET24] [Start Date:11.76] [End Date:76.59] [Processing Status:2012-01-31] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "15F46A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "AMS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "AGROMET08"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "AGROMET08"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:15F46A]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "2010-12-31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "22.70"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "MADHYA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AMS] [Product:Zonal Agricultural Research Station, Powerkhed, Hoshangabad] [Product Description:MADHYA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F46A] [Temporal Resolution:AGROMET08] [Start Date:22.70] [End Date:77.74] [Processing Status:2010-12-31] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "15F016"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "ISRO0022"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "ISRO0022"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "2007-11-26"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "11.40] [End Date:92.64"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:ISTRAC, Dolly gunj, port blair] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F016] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO0022] [Start Date:11.40] [End Date:92.64] [Processing Status:2007-11-26] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "15F114"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "ISRO0276"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "ISRO0276"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "2008-04-22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "11.40"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is INS Utkroash,Port Blair?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:INS Utkroash,Port Blair] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F114] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO0276] [Start Date:11.40] [End Date:92.60] [Processing Status:2008-04-22] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "15F115"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "ISRO0277"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "ISRO0277"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "2009-01-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "8.00"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:INS Kardip,Kamorta Island,PB] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F115] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO0277] [Start Date:8.00] [End Date:93.50] [Processing Status:2009-01-01] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "15F22B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "ISRO0555"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "ISRO0555"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "2011-02-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "11.63] [End Date:92.74"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:Pondicherry University-Port Blair (NON-ISRO)] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F22B] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO0555] [Start Date:11.63] [End Date:92.74] [Processing Status:2011-02-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "15F505"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "ISRO1285"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "ISRO1285"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:15F505]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "NA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "9.18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Car Nicobar?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:Car Nicobar] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F505] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1285] [Start Date:9.18] [End Date:92.82] [Processing Status:NA] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "15F506"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "ISRO1286"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "ISRO1286"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "2010-11-28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "7.01] [End Date:93.94"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Campbellbay?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:Campbellbay] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F506] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1286] [Start Date:7.01] [End Date:93.94] [Processing Status:2010-11-28] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Teressa?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Teressa?",
        "answer": "15F507"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Teressa?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Teressa?",
        "answer": "ISRO1287"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Teressa?",
        "answer": "ISRO1287"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Teressa?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Teressa?",
        "answer": "2010-12-23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Teressa?",
        "answer": "8.30] [End Date:93.13"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Teressa?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Teressa?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:Teressa] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F507] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1287] [Start Date:8.30] [End Date:93.13] [Processing Status:2010-12-23] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Katchal?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Katchal?",
        "answer": "15F508"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Katchal?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Katchal?",
        "answer": "ISRO1288"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Katchal?",
        "answer": "ISRO1288"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Katchal?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Katchal?",
        "answer": "NA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Katchal?",
        "answer": "8.00] [End Date:93.38"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Katchal?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Katchal?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:Katchal] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F508] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1288] [Start Date:8.00] [End Date:93.38] [Processing Status:NA] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Hutbay?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Hutbay?",
        "answer": "15F509"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Hutbay?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Hutbay?",
        "answer": "ISRO1289"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Hutbay?",
        "answer": "ISRO1289"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Hutbay?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Hutbay?",
        "answer": "2015-11-04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Hutbay?",
        "answer": "10.60] [End Date:92.54"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Hutbay?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Hutbay?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:Hutbay] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F509] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1289] [Start Date:10.60] [End Date:92.54] [Processing Status:2015-11-04] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Havelock?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Havelock?",
        "answer": "15F50A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Havelock?",
        "answer": "AWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Havelock?",
        "answer": "ISRO1290"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Havelock?",
        "answer": "ISRO1290"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Havelock?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Havelock?",
        "answer": "2015-11-04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Havelock?",
        "answer": "12.04] [End Date:92.98"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Havelock?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Havelock?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWS] [Product:Havelock] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F50A] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1290] [Start Date:12.04] [End Date:92.98] [Processing Status:2015-11-04] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160001"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI001"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI001"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.57"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:AAU, BACA, Anand, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160001] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI001] [Start Date:22.57] [End Date:72.93] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160002"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI002"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI002"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.59"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:AAU, NARP, Arnej, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160002] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI002] [Start Date:22.59] [End Date:72.27] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160003"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI003"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI003"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.83"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:AAU, Agri. Research Stn, Dahod, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160003] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI003] [Start Date:22.83] [End Date:74.27] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160004"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI004"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI004"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.82"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:AAU, Maize Research Stn, Godhra, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160004] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI004] [Start Date:22.82] [End Date:73.67] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160005"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI005"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI005"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.30"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:AAU, Model Farm, Vadodara, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160005] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI005] [Start Date:22.30] [End Date:73.20] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160006"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI006"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI006"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.80"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:AAU, Main Rice Research Station, Thasara, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160006] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI006] [Start Date:22.80] [End Date:72.57] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160007"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI007"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI007"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "23.12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:AAU, Agri. Res Stn, Viramgam, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160007] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI007] [Start Date:23.12] [End Date:72.03] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160008"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI008"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI008"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "21.50"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:JAU, Junagadh, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160008] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI008] [Start Date:21.50] [End Date:70.44] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "160009"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI009"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI009"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.34"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:JAU, Targhadia, Rajkot, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:160009] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI009] [Start Date:22.34] [End Date:70.91] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "16000A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AWSAGRI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI010"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "AGRI010"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "2010-05-16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "22.47"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSAGRI] [Product:JAU, Jamnagar, Gujarat] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:16000A] [Temporal Resolution:AGRI010] [Start Date:22.47] [End Date:70.03] [Processing Status:2010-05-16] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "15F670"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "ISRO1648"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "ISRO1648"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "2021-02-05"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "11.64] [End Date:92.71"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "ANDAMAN & NICOBAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is ISTRC-Portblair?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:ISTRC-Portblair] [Product Description:ANDAMAN & NICOBAR] [Processing Level:15F670] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1648] [Start Date:11.64] [End Date:92.71] [Processing Status:2021-02-05] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "15F65E"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "ISRO1630"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "ISRO1630"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "13.46] [End Date:79.17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is NARL-Gadanki?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:NARL-Gadanki] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F65E] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1630] [Start Date:13.46] [End Date:79.17] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "15F661"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1633"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1633"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "13.78"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SHAR-2(LPSC)?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:SHAR-2(LPSC)] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F661] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1633] [Start Date:13.78] [End Date:80.25] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "15F662"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1634"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1634"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "13.70] [End Date:80.23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SHAR-1(FM Building)?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:SHAR-1(FM Building)] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F662] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1634] [Start Date:13.70] [End Date:80.23] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "15F664"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1636"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1636"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "13.73] [End Date:80.17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SHAR-4(Phase-2)?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:SHAR-4(Phase-2)] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F664] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1636] [Start Date:13.73] [End Date:80.17] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "15F665"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1637"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "ISRO1637"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "13.70"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SHAR-3(KRP Colony)?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:SHAR-3(KRP Colony)] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:15F665] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1637] [Start Date:13.70] [End Date:80.03] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "15F66A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "ISRO1642"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "ISRO1642"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:15F66A]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "2020-09-04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "28.61] [End Date:77.18"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is Delhi Earth Station?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:Delhi Earth Station] [Product Description:DELHI] [Processing Level:15F66A] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1642] [Start Date:28.61] [End Date:77.18] [Processing Status:2020-09-04] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "15F657"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "ISRO1623"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "ISRO1623"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:15F657]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "23.04"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:SAC-BopalCampus-Ahmedabad] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:15F657] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1623] [Start Date:23.04] [End Date:72.45] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "15F658"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "ISRO1624"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "ISRO1624"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:15F658]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "23.02"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SAC-Main Campus?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:SAC-Main Campus] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:15F658] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1624] [Start Date:23.02] [End Date:72.51] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "15F65C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "AWSUPG"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "ISRO1628"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "ISRO1628"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:15F65C]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "2020-07-27"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "23.04] [End Date:72.49"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "Product:PRL-Ahmedabad] [Product Description:GUJARAT"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is PRL-Ahmedabad?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:AWSUPG] [Product:PRL-Ahmedabad] [Product Description:GUJARAT] [Processing Level:15F65C] [Temporal Resolution:ISRO1628] [Start Date:23.04] [End Date:72.49] [Processing Status:2020-07-27] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "1415E0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "IDME1504"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "IDME1504"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "18.83"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is JAGTIYAL_AGRO?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:JAGTIYAL_AGRO] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415E0] [Temporal Resolution:IDME1504] [Start Date:18.83] [End Date:78.93] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "16914C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "IMDB0332"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "IMDB0332"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "17.45] [End Date:78.47"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MET_HYDERABAD?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:MET_HYDERABAD] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:16914C] [Temporal Resolution:IMDB0332] [Start Date:17.45] [End Date:78.47] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "1415CC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "IMDE1484"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "IMDE1484"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "18.01] [End Date:79.60"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "Product:WARANGAL] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is WARANGAL?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:WARANGAL] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415CC] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1484] [Start Date:18.01] [End Date:79.60] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "1415CD"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "IMDE1485"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "IMDE1485"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "17.24] [End Date:81.10"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is ASWARAOPET?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:ASWARAOPET] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415CD] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1485] [Start Date:17.24] [End Date:81.10] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "1415CE"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "IMDE1486"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "IMDE1486"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "16.85"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is KAMPASAGAR?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:KAMPASAGAR] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415CE] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1486] [Start Date:16.85] [End Date:79.47] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "1415CF"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "IMDE1487"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "IMDE1487"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "17.62"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is SANGAREDDY_AGRO?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:SANGAREDDY_AGRO] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415CF] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1487] [Start Date:17.62] [End Date:74.07] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with TANDUR?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of TANDUR?",
        "answer": "1415D0"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for TANDUR?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of TANDUR?",
        "answer": "IMDE1488"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of TANDUR?",
        "answer": "IMDE1488"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in TANDUR?",
        "answer": "Temporal Resolution:IMDE1488]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of TANDUR?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for TANDUR?",
        "answer": "17.21] [End Date:77.58"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of TANDUR?",
        "answer": "ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is TANDUR?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:TANDUR] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415D0] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1488] [Start Date:17.21] [End Date:77.58] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "1415D1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "IMDE1489"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "IMDE1489"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "16.63] [End Date:81.74"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is MARUTERU?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:MARUTERU] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415D1] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1489] [Start Date:16.63] [End Date:81.74] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "In-situ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "1415D2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "IMDE1490"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "IMDE1490"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "13.61"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is PERUMALLAPALLE?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:PERUMALLAPALLE] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415D2] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1490] [Start Date:13.61] [End Date:79.34] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "1415D3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "IMDAWS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "IMDE1491"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "IMDE1491"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "[Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "2011-08-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "15.45] [End Date:78.46"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "Product"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is NANDYAL?",
        "answer": "[Category:in-situ] [Satellite:In-situ] [Sensor:IMDAWS] [Product:NANDYAL] [Product Description:ANDHRA PRADESH] [Processing Level:1415D3] [Temporal Resolution:IMDE1491] [Start Date:15.45] [End Date:78.46] [Processing Status:2011-08-09] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "Cheerapunji"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "S BAND DWR CHERRAPUNJI"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "Product Description:DWR Data for Cheerapunji"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "2016-05-20"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "DWR Data for Cheerapunji"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is RSCHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Category:radar] [Satellite:RADAR] [Sensor:S BAND DWR CHERRAPUNJI] [Product:RSCHR_L2B_STD] [Product Description:DWR Data for Cheerapunji] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:10 MINUTES] [Start Date:2016-05-20] [End Date:2022-11-05] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "SHAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "S BAND DWR SHAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "Product Description:DWR Data for SHAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "2018-08-30"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "DWR Data for SHAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is RSSHR_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Category:radar] [Satellite:RADAR] [Sensor:S BAND DWR SHAR] [Product:RSSHR_L2B_STD] [Product Description:DWR Data for SHAR] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:10 MINUTES] [Start Date:2018-08-30] [End Date:2023-03-31] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "RADAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "L2B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "TERLS C BAND"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:10 MINUTES]"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "2016-03-09"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "Standard products from TERLS Doppler weather radar"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is RCTLS_L2B_STD?",
        "answer": "[Category:radar] [Satellite:RADAR] [Sensor:TERLS C BAND] [Product:RCTLS_L2B_STD] [Product Description:Standard products from TERLS Doppler weather radar received at every 10 minutes interval] [Processing Level:L2B] [Temporal Resolution:10 MINUTES] [Start Date:2016-03-09] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the satellite name associated with RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "RADAR"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing level of RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "L2C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sensor is used for RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "TERLS C BAND"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temporal resolution of RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spatial resolution of RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "10 MINUTES"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the parameters included in RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "corrected reflectivity(DBZ) and radial velocity(VEL)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the processing status of RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "Active"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the start and end date for RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "2023-09-01"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the description of RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "Volumetric gridded data of TERLS DWR"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is RCTLS_L2C_VOL?",
        "answer": "[Category:radar] [Satellite:RADAR] [Sensor:TERLS C BAND] [Product:RCTLS_L2C_VOL] [Product Description:Volumetric gridded data of TERLS DWR,using DPRF mode files only,containing corrected reflectivity(DBZ) and radial velocity(VEL)] [Processing Level:L2C] [Temporal Resolution:10 MINUTES] [Start Date:2023-09-01] [End Date:2025-03-11] [Processing Status:Active] "
    }
]